greenandgoldrugby.com 2012-06-10

# Privacy Policy - Green and Gold Rugby Blog

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policyin order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and make useof personal information. The following outlines our Privacy Policy.

When accessing our Website, Green and Gold Rugby will learn certain information aboutyou during your visit.

Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technologycalled "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?")and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Informationgathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time ofvisits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visitedjust before and just after our Web site, your IP address.

 **What Are Cookies?**

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous uniqueidentifier. When you visit a Web site, that site's computer asks your computerfor permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specificallydesignated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browserif your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browseronly permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, notthe cookies sent to you by other sites.

 **IP Addresses**

IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to theInternet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the networkto identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our webserver as part of demographic and profile data known as “traffic data”so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.

 **Email Information**

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the contentof your email messages together with your email address and our responses. Weprovide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employin the maintenance of information received online, mail and telephone.

 **How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?**

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administeringour business activities, providing customer service and making available otheritems and services to our customers and prospective customers.

Green and Gold Rugby will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when youvisit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us, nor willsuch information be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third partieswithout the approval of the user at the time of collection.

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words,when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protectionof our legal rights.

 **  
A Special Note About Children**

Children are not eligible to use our web site and services and we ask thatminors (under the age of 13) do not submit any personal information to us. Ifyou are a minor, you can use this site only in conjunction with permission andguidance from your parents or guardians.

 **How Do We Protect Your Information and Secure Information Transmissions?**

Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason,we request that you do not send private information to us by email. However,doing so is allowed, but at your own risk. Some of the information you may enteron our Web site may be transmitted securely via a secure medium known as SecureSockets Layer, or SSL. Credit Card information is never transmitted via email.

Green and Gold Rugby may use software programs to create summary statistics, which are usedfor such purposes as assessing the number of visitors to the different sectionsof our site, what information is of most and least interest, determining technicaldesign specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas.

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains availableto all users, Green and Gold Rugby uses software programs to monitor network traffic to identifyunauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.

 **Policy Changes**

We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or withoutnotice. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in thefuture, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us underthis Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this PrivacyPolicy, without your prior consent.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principlesin order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protectedand maintained.

 **  
Contact**

If you have any questions regarding this Policy, or your dealings with ourweb site, please [contact us](http://www.greenandgoldrugby.com/contact-us).

Green and Gold Rugby
